Contact

yadelskyiviktor@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/viktoryadelskyi (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

React.js

JavaScript

TypeScript

Languages

English (B1+)

Ukrainian (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

React. Lite level

React JS. Practical Course 2020 (Hooks, Classes, Redux)

JavaScript v.2.0

Viktor Yadelskyi

Software Engineer | Frontend Developer

Lviv, Lviv, Ukraine

Summary

I have a master's degree in computer science and more than three years of web development experience. I'm experienced in building and maintaining responsive websites. I possess proficient knowledge of main frontend technologies: JavaScript, React, React Hooks, Redux; Also I know how to work with: CSS preprocessors (SASS/LESS),Bootstrap,FlexBox, Grid, Ajax, npm/yarn, webpack, and Git. For all of my works, I have maintained one common thing, i.e, cleanness. My code is always well structured so that any child can easily follow along with it. Finally, I try to think of the targeted audience and code accordingly by fully understanding the flow and logic.

Experience

EPAM Systems

2 years 3 months

Trainee Software Engineer

February 2023 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Lviv, Lviv, Ukraine

Student Software Engineer

January 2022 - February 2023 (1 year 2 months)

Lviv, Lviv, Ukraine

Freelance

Frontend Engineer

July 2021 - October 2021 (4 months)

I took part in a short-term commercial project in the e-commerce domain. My responsibilities included creating markup and writing front-end logic by using React.

The team had 2 FE devs (including me) and 1 BE.

Main technologies used by me: TypeScript, React (with hooks), CSS preprocessor (SCSS), Webpack.

Education

Ternopil Ivan Puluj National Technical University Master's degree, Computer Science · (2019)

Ternopil State 'Ivan Pul'uj' Technical University Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2018)